Can love overcome the past?
After We Collided is a romance, drama film directed by Roger Kumble.
Tessa finds herself struggling with her complicated relationship with Hardin;
she faces a dilemma that could change their lives forever.
Tessa Young, played by Josephine Langford.
Hardin Scott, played by Hero Fiennes Tiffin.
Trevor Matthews, played by Dylan Sprouse.
Trish Daniels, played by Louise Lombard.
Christian Vance, played by Charlie Weber.
Kimberly Vance, played by Candice King.
After We Collided is a 2020 American romantic drama film directed by Roger Kumble from a screenplay
by Anna Todd and Mario Celaya, based on the 2014 novel of the same name by Todd.
It is the sequel to After (2019) and the second
installment in the After film series.
The film stars Josephine Langford and Hero Fiennes Tiffin reprising their roles as Tessa Young and Hardin Scott, respectively, with Dylan
Sprouse, Shane Paul McGhie, Candice King, Khadijha Red Thunder, Inanna Sarkis, Samuel Larsen, and Selma Blair in supporting roles.
After We Collided premiered in Europe on September 2, 2020, and was released simultaneously in
theaters and video-on-demand in the United States on October 23, by Open Road Films.
Like its predecessor, the film received negative reviews from critics, with many
criticizing the screenplay and glamourized portrayal of toxic relationships.
Despite this, it was a box-office success, grossing $48
million worldwide against a $14 million budget.
A sequel, After We Fell, was released in 2021.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, love, teenage crush.
The tone is emotional.